

CARLOS HINOJOSA PINTO

20/07/1998

https://www.carlosh.ch

AARAU, AARGAU (SWITZERLAND) EU CITIZEN RESIDENCE PERMIT B

ABOUT ME

I am a Computer Engineer graduated from the Polytechnic University of Valencia in Spain, with more than 3 years of experience in the field. I love learning new things and acquiring new skills every day. In my free time, I enjoy reading, going to the gym, and trail running.

TECH SKILLS

Computer Languages:

- JavaScript/Typescript
- PHP
- Python
- HTML/CSS

Tecnologies:

- React
- Node JS
- Docker
- NextJS
- Laravel
- Jest

- NextJS
- Drupal
- Git
- Mongo DB
- MySQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Agile methodologies
- · Teamwork and collaboration
- · Goal-oriented mindset

Languages:

- Spanish (Native)
- English (B2)
- German (A1 and currently learning)

CONTACT

+41 78 212 90 07 carloshin98@gmail.com https://www.carlosh.es/en

EXPERIENCE

SIA CH

Fullstack developer

May 2023 - Now

Developing, and maintaining both the front-end and back-end components of various software applications. I collaborate closely with cross-functional teams, including designers and project managers, to ensure the successful implementation of projects.

Technologies used:

JavaScript React Docker Git Linux PHP Jest MySQL

IOBUILDERS

Frontend developer

September 2021 - May 2023

Development of a NFTs marketplace for DC comics on the palm blockchain, in charge of implementing different functionalities on the front end of the web. Making deployments to the different environments. Also doing unit tests for each component of the application. All this through SCRUM planning with the use of Jira and with daily meetings with people in different time zones.

Technologies used:

JavaScript Typescript React Docker Git Linux Gitlab CI/CD Jest

NTT DATA

Frontend developer

November 2020 - September 2021

Working for different projects at the front end and also maintaining the database. Performing unit and functional testing for different web flows. Using agile methodology.

Technologies used:

JavaScript Typescript Docker Angular React Git Linux MySql

MULTISCAN TECHNOLOGIES (INTERNSHIP)

Software developer

January 2020 - May 2020

Software development for fruit and vegetable sorting machines. Capturing and handling images to train neural networks and detect defects using AI.

Technologies used:

C++ Python Git Linux

ACTIVALINK (INTERNSHIP)

Fullstack developer

March 2019- September 2019

Development of functionalities for different websites of different companies. Also bug fixes in production in different technologies and managing databases

Technologies used:

React Javascript Typescript NodeJS PHP Laravel Mysql

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering Degree

Polytechnic University of Valencia http://www.upv.es September 2016 - June 2020

PROJECTS

TFG

https://www.tfg.carlosh.es/app/

Final project for the Computer Engineering Degree. This web allow you to order food from a restaurant. Done with **PHP** and **React**.

WEB MIGUEL PINTO https://miguel-pinto.vercel.app/

Web made in **NextJS** and **Typescript** for the promotion of the painter Miguel Pinto.

WEB CARS https://sell-car-carlosh.vercel.app/cars

Marketplace to buy/sell cars , using $\mbox{\bf Typescript},$ $\mbox{\bf React},$ $\mbox{\bf NextJS}$ and $\mbox{\bf Supabase}.$